Guide to the Fredericka Martin Photograph Collection ALBA.PHOTO.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Photographs, circa 1937-1938
  - Clipping: "Nurses Return from Spain", Fanny Golub, Lenora Temple, Cleo Cannon Duncan, Anna Taft, Mary Rader, Edythe May Dyer, SS Aquitania, Sep 2, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Cohen, Alex: At Examination/Operating Table, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Cohen, Alex: Group, Leon Muldavin, Monroe NY, Apr 28, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Cohen, Alex: Group, Unidentified, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Contact Sheet: Surgery and Panoramas, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Contact Sheets: Misc., circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Cordoba Hospital [?]: Building, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Davidovich, Antoni: Group, Dr. Semet and Unidentified Medical Personnel, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Davidovich, Antoni: Group, Unidentified Doctors, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Davidovich, Antoni: Operating on a Patient, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Davidovich, Antoni: Portrait, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Davidow, Ruth: On Burro, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Davidson, David: Contact Sheet with Portraits and Group, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Davidson, David: Portrait, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - de la Mora, Constancia: Gravesite, Cuernavaca, Mexico, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - de la Mora, Constancia: Augusto Varilieurio Okorokova, Spain, Apr 26, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - de la Mora, Constancia: ?, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - de la Mora, Constancia: Portrait, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Demonstrations/Parades/Rallies: Castillejo, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Demonstrations/Parades/Rallies: Group, Dr. Langer, [J?É¬?zef?] Heller, Gustav Gundelach, ?, Albacete, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Demonstrations/Parades/Rallies: Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Demonstrations/Parades/Rallies: United States, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Devine, John M. (Jack): Portrait, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Dhago, Joseph, Elena Zu?É¬±iga: With Dog, Lima, Peru, Nov 1, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Dhago, Joseph: John Leopold Simon and ?, Release from Tarraza Hospital, Barcelona, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Dhago, Joseph: Mois?É¬©s Vall?É¬©s Broggi and Alfonso Denia, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Dhago, Joseph: Federico S?É¬°nchez Cavanillas and John Leopold Simon, Terraza Hospital, Barcelona, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Dhago, Joseph: Edward Barsky, Cuevas Labradas, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Dhago, Joseph: Michael Tabaka, Jose Maria Vinueza, ? Malaga, ? Amador, Timoteo Moreno, Jose Jordana, Mois?É¬©s Vall?É¬©s Broggi, Paro Vargas, Esther Goldstein, Carmen ?, Felipe ?, Puebla de Hijar, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Dhago, Joseph: Dr. Serudu, Plaza de Catalu?É¬±a, Barcelona, Oct 1, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Dhago, Joseph: Socorro Rojo Internacional No.1, Rocha Pinto, Borris (Polaco), Lisolete ?, Albacete Hospital, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Dhago, Joseph: Spanish Medical Personnel, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Dhago, Joseph: Teniente Alfonso Denia, Captain Boulkar [Simon Boulka?], Commander Bush, Mois?É¬©s Vall?É¬©s Broggi, Alconiza Hospital, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Dhago, Joseph: Teniente Alfonso Denia, Captain Boulkar [Simon Boulka?], Commander Bush, Mois?É¬©s Vall?É¬©s Broggi, Azaila Hospital, Oct 1, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Dhago, Joseph: Group, Unidentified, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Dhago, Joseph: Portrait, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Dhago, Joseph: Shipboard on S.S. Aquitania with Cesar Ferrerra en route to Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Dhago, Joseph: Shipboard on S.S. Aquitania with Cesar Ferrerra and Two Cuban Pilots in Civilian Clothes en route to Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Diaz, Jos?É¬©: Portrait, Photographic Postcard, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Dodds, Isabella and Ren?É¬©: Nurses, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Donova, Donald, Portrait, [NYC?], circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Dumont, Ren?É¬©: Portrait, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Dumont, Ren?É¬©: Riding Horse, Colemenar, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Durem, Ramen (Ramon): Portrait, Villa Paz, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Durham, Rebecca: Evacuation to Cordoba, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Dutch Volunteers: Group, Unidentified, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Dyer, May Edyth: Anne Taft [?], Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Dyer, May Edyth: Group, Unidentified, Cordoba, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Dyer, May Edyth: Portrait, Spain, Apr 21, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Edward K. Barsky Hospital: Buildings, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 61a)
  - Eloesser, Leo: D. Harcourt, [Teruel?], circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Eloesser, Leo: Group, Operating, Manuel ?, Leonard H. Larsen, Antonio Pelegrini, Alice Wagnon, Matar?É¬?, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Eloesser, Leo: Group, Operating Room, Manuel ?, Cleo Duncan, Antonio Pelegrini, Alice Wagnon, Unidentified Doctor, Matar?É¬?, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Eloesser, Leo: Setting a Cast, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Eloesser, Leo: Group, Unidentified, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Eloesser, Leo: West Coast Group, Anne Bruzzichesi and three Unidentified Nurses, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Eloesser, Leo: Photographic Positives of Magazine/Newspaper Articles, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Eloesser, Leo: Portrait, [NYC?], circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Enguite, Agustin: Portrait, Valencia, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Epstein, Ruth Wilson: Group, Rose Margaret Harvan and Two Nurses, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Epstein, Ruth: Groups, Unidentified, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Epstein, Ruth: Sleeping, Prior to Crossing the Ebro or Teruel Front, Apr 21, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Erickson, Thelma: Group, Unidentified Patients, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Erickson, Thelma: Swimming at the Beach, Port Bou, Catalonia, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Ettleson, Abraham: Group, Marcus Fried, Ernst Amann, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Ewert, Andreas and Olga: In Front of International Brigade Sanidad Buildings, Apr 20, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Fajans, Wolf: Group, Unidentified, U.S. [?], Feb 1, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Farwell Dinner: Edward Barsky and Walter B. Cannon, Autumn 1937 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Ferrer, Arturo: Cuban Volunteer on Troop Train, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Film Team: Two Men, One Woman, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Fine, Arturo: Portrait, Spain, Apr 21, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Fischer, Louis: Group, ? Ansell, Spain, Apr 21, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Fishman, Moses "Moe": Group, Unidentified, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Flett, Harold: At the Front, Non-Combat, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Fontaine, Dorothy: with Husband, Not in Spain, undated (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Fontaine, Dorothy: Group, Unidentified, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Fontaine, Dorothy: Group, Norman C. Mintz and Unidentified Man, Cerbere (France), circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Fontaine, Dorothy: Portrait, NYC, undated (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Fontaine, Dorothy: Residence, U.S., undated (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Franklin, Samuel: On Board S.S. Aquitania, en route to Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Freed, Rose: Group, Lenora Temple, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Freeman, Helen: Clipping, On Board Ile de France, Returning from Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Freeman, Helen: Group, Alice Wagnon, Benicasim, Apr 20, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Freeman, Helen: On Board Ile de France, Returning from Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - French Cities: Cerbere, Train Station, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - French Cities: Le Havre, Waterfront, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - French Cities: Port Bou, Panorama, undated (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - French Troops: Africa, undated (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - French Volunteers: Filming with Swedish Ambulance, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Fuentes, Tan: Group, Scott Alexander Torrance, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Fuhr (De Vries), Lini M.: Dr. Crookston, Return from Spain, May 1, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Fuhr (De Vries), Lini M.: Family and Friends, Not in Spain, undated (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Fuhr (De Vries), Lini M.: Fredericka Martin, Edward Barsky, Not in Spain, undated (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Fuhr (De Vries), Lini M.: Group, Holding Baby, Two Unidentified Women, Four Unidentified Men, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Fuhr (De Vries), Lini M.: Portrait of Modesta Morat(?), Inscribed to Fuhr, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Fuhr (De Vries), Lini M.: Return Interview, Helene Weissman and Six Unidentified Women, United States, undated (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Fuhr (De Vries), Lini M.: Robert J. Raven (on Stretcher) and Frank Ayers, circa 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Gandall, Bill: Portrait, Not in Spain, undated (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Garibaldi Battalion: Shipboard, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Gates, John: Group, Stefan Temple and Three Others next to Ambulance, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - German-Austrian Volunteers: Playing Chess (in Hospital?), Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Goland, Philip Pakier: Behind the Lines, Daily Life of the Soldiers, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Goland, Philip Pakier: Group, ?, ?, Volunteers, Cordoba Front, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Goland, Philip Pakier: Portrait, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Goldblatt, Rose Sara: Family, U.S., undated (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Goldblatt, Rose Sara: Group, Toby Jensky, Unidentified Medical Personnel and Spanish Children, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Goldblatt, Rose: Unidentified Man, Villa Paz, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Goldin, Irene: Attending to Patient, Teruel Front, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Goldstein, Jack: Portrait, Spain [?], undated (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Golub, Rudy: At Memorial with ?, ?, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - [Gomez?], Gus: Post-Civil War, Huete, undated (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - [Gomez?], Gus: In Boat with Unidentified Soldier, Pebere, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - G?É¬?mez, Sebastian: Family, Not in Spain, undated (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - G?É¬?mez, Sebastian: Group, In Small Boat, Cerbere (France), Apr 20, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - G?É¬?mez, Sebastian: Group, Unidentified Woman, Paris, [1937] (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Green, Nan: Group, "Juanito", Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - [Greenbladt?], Jacques: On Terrace with Unidentified Group, Matar?É¬?, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Groups: Unidentified, Benicasim, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Group: Unidentified, Not in Spain, Sep 1, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Groups: Unidentified, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - Gunter, Pedro: Portrait, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - Hamilton, Robert: Plucking a Chicken with Beryl Smithson and [Fredericka Martin?], Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - [Hard?], Alva: Portrait, [Spain?], May 25, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Harris (Marantz), Ray: Group, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Harris (Marantz), Ray: Group, Spanish Aides and Nurses, Villa Paz, Apr 20, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Harris (Marantz), Ray: Group, Mataro Hospital Nurses and Recovering Patient, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Harris (Marantz), Ray: Group, Unidentified, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Harris (Marantz), Ray: Shipboard, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Harris (Marantz), Ray: Shipboard, Grace Berkowitz, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Harris (Marantz), Ray: Shipboard, Hilda Bell, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Harris (Marantz), Ray: Shipboard, ? Howehound, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Harris (Marantz), Ray: Smoking a Cigarette, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Harris (Marantz), Ray: Surgery, with Two Doctors and One Nurse, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Hartman, Hernine: Dr. Anka (a.k.a. Adela Bohunicki), Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Hartman, Hernine: Santa Cruz, CA, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Haywood, Harry: with Two Others, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Hecht, Joe: Rest and Relaxation, Nov 1, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Hefetz, Pinchas: Portrait, "The Blind Palestinian", circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 16a)
  - Henderson, Bessie: Portraits, Including Childhood, Not in Spain, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Hene, Julius: Ambulance Crew, Daniel White, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Hernaiz, Dulcea: Group, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Hernfeld, Victor: Driver and Truck in Background, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Hevran, Rose: Portrait, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Hill, Michael: Glen ? and Bill ?, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Hill, Michael: Philip Pakier Goland, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Hine, Dr.: Behind the Lines, Rest and Relaxation, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Holst, Wilhelm: Group, Scandinavian Assistants, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Hospital: Operating Room, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Hospital: Operating Room, Automobile Headlights used for Surgery, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Hospital: Operating Room, Blood Transfusion, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Hospital: Recovery Ward, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Hospital Universidad: Murcia, Apr 20, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Hourihan, Martin William: Behind the Lines, Rest and Relaxation, with Rebecca Shulman, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Hourihan, Martin William: Injured in Hospital, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Hourihan, Martin William: with Unidentified Man, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - [Hull?], Michael: Group, Madrid, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Hutchins, Evelyn: Group, Karl Rahman with Three Others, Villa Paz, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Ibarruri, Dolores: Portrait, Photographic Postcard, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Individuals: Unidentified, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Individuals: Unidentified, Benicasim, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - International Brigade Reunion: Group, Bobigny (France), Dec 4, 1975-Dec 5, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - International Brigade Tunnel: Cerbere (France), May 1, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Jelly, John: Group, Tommy Kerr, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Jensky, Toby: At the Beach, Cerbere (France), circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Jensky, Toby: At the Front, Non-Combat, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Jensky, Toby: Helene Weissman, Spain, Apr 20, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Jensky, Toby: [Major Johnston?], Villa Paz, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Jensky, Toby: Unidentified Man, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Jensky, Toby: Lunch with Unidentified, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Jensky, Toby: Shipboard with Unidentified Man, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - ?, Jerry: Group, Fernanda ? and Four Others with Truck, Villa Paz, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - ?, Jerry: Juggling, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - ?, Jerry: Portrait, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Jolly, John: Group, Tommy Kerr, Villa Paz, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Jolly, John: Portrait, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Kaliskov?É¬°, Marie: Home with Dog, Not in Spain, undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Kaliskov?É¬°, Marie: Group, ? Hurkov?É¬° and Unidentified Man, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Kaliskov?É¬°, Marie: Portrait, Spain, undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Kee, Salaria (a.k.a. Salaria Kea, later O'Reilly): Portrait, NYC, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Keen, Harry: Family, Not in Spain, undated (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Kerr, Tommy: with Three Spanish Women (?), circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Kerr, Tommy: Group, Unidentified Women, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Kerr, Tommy: Portrait, with Fernanda ?, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Kisch, Bedrich: Portrait, Not in Spain, undated (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Klein, Jack: Bullet-Ridden Ambulance, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Kornbloom, Morris: Shipboard, Three Unidentified Men, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Kozar, John: Portraits, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Kristanov, Tsvetan Angelov (a.k.a. Oscar Telge): Instructing at S.S.I., Clippings, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Kristanov, Tsvetan Angelov (a.k.a. Oscar Telge): Portraits, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Kuferberg, Simon: Sweeping, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Landeta Valchina, Juan: Portrait, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Langer, Walter: May McFarlane, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Larson, Thurs Arvid: Ruth Davidow, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Lasgarter, Larry: Group, Unidentified, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Lawson, Jean Watt: Portraits, Not in Spain, undated (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Leigh, J.: Behind the Lines, Daily Life of the Soldiers, Villa Paz, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Lending, Edward: At Home, [U.S.?], undated (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Lending, Edward: with Two Volunteers (?), Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Les, Benjamin: Sawing a Log, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Levin, May: Evacuation Train from Benicasim to Catalonia, Apr 1, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Levine, Ralph: Group, Jane Mariou and Two Unidentified Women and One Unidentified Man on Pier, [Spain?], Jan 1, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Levine, ?: May Levine's Son, undated (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Locomotive/Troop Train: Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Lopez, Epiphanio: Portrait, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Lopez, Margarita: At Home with Lenliade Kerseler, near Calmerar El Viejo, May 26, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - McFarland, May: Shipboard, Aug 1, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Malbin, Barney: with Three Women, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Malbin, Barney: Portrait, Benicasim, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Malbin, Barney: Portrait, Valencia, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Malbin, Barney and Virginia: Behind the Lines, Rest and Relaxation, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Margolies, Grace: Shipboard, Moe Fishman, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Margolies, Grace: Shipboard with ?, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Martin, Alice Wagnon: Writing Surgery Schedule on Blackboard, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Martin, Fredericka: In Front of Ambulance with Unidentified Man, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - [Martin, Fredericka?]: Photographic Postcard with Unidentified Man, Not in Spain, undated (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Martin, Fredericka: Portrait, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Martin, Fredericka: Shipboard, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Martin, Fredericka: Group, Unidentified Woman and Donkey, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Martinez, ?: Portrait, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Maas, Johana (Jopie): Residence, The Netherlands, May 23, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Mataro Hospital: Groups, ?, May Edythe Dyer, Mark ?, ?, Anne Taft, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Mataro Hospital: Groups, Unidentified, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Matthews, Herbert: Humberto Galiani, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Meana, Carmen: Portrait, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Medical Personnel: Abraham Ettleson, Florence Pike (a.k.a. Florence Mildred Tew) and ?, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Medical Personnel: Ambulance Crew, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Medical Personnel: Ambulance Crew, Drivers, Leonardo Alvarez, Aurelio Perez, George Zlatovski, Ives D. Jacquie, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Medical Personnel: Barcelona Infirmary Group, Dr. Kanelu and ?, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Medical Personnel: Battalion 57, Salvador Guardiola, Alfonso Denia, FaU.S.to Gonzalez, J. Kizzely, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Medical Personnel: Beryl Smithson, Pat ?, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Medical Personnel: Casa Rafa, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Medical Personnel: ?, Cresserin ?, Tommy Kerr, Villa Paz, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Medical Personnel: Czechoslovakian, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Medical Personnel: Doctor Receiving Gift from Spanish Villagers, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Medical Personnel: Dutch, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Medical Personnel: Dutch, Group, ?, Simon d'Ancona, Maatje Husinga, An Blaquw, Johana (Jopie) Maas, Noortje, Jose Maria de Semprun y Gurrea, Jet Adrainse, Jenny ?, Jenny's Husband, Trudy de Vries, Sempron's Daughter, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Medical Personnel: Edna Sanford, Jack Devine, Charles de Svelskoe, ?, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Medical Personnel: Edward Barsky and Ren?É¬© Dumont, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Medical Personnel: Erica ?, German Nurse, Ray Harris, Vich, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Medical Personnel: Fredericka Martin, Irving Busch, Unidentified Spanish (?) Man, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Medical Personnel: Grace Margolies, Crescencia ?, Salaria Kee (a.k.a. Salaria Kea), Hijar de Puebla, Apr 21, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Medical Personnel: Group, Dulcea Hernandez, ?, Rose Weiner, and Unidentified Children, Benicasim, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Medical Personnel: Group, Helen Freeman, Ray Harris, Lini M. De Vries, and 3 Unidentified Individuals, Barcelona, Mar 2, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Medical Personnel: Group, Hermine Hartman, Ruth Epstein, Hilda ?, Lisa ?, Edyth May Dyer, and ?, ? (Nurses), Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Medical Personnel: Group, Ives Jacqurier, ?, Jack Goldstein, with Two Others, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Medical Personnel: Group, Joe Hecht (Taking Photo), Beryl Smithson, Pat ?, ?, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Medical Personnel: Rose Harvahn with Two Others, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Medical Personnel: Group, Unidentified, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Medical Personnel: Group, Unidentified, Benicasim, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Medical Personnel: Laboratory Technicians, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Medical Personnel: Lenora Temple, Toby Jensky, ?, Al Goldberg, Mark Straus, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Medical Personnel: Major Johnson [Ramen (Ray) Durem?], Anne Schuldiner, Morris Kornblum, Davie Jones, John Jolly, Stephen Flaherty?, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Medical Personnel: Major Johnson [Ramen (Ray) Durem?], Morris Kornblum, Anne Schuldiner, Stephen Flaherty (?), circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Medical Personnel: Mark Straus, Toby Jensky, Selma Chadwick, Lenora Temple, Teruel, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Medical Personnel: Mike Ehrenberg and English Nurse, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 31)